

#### SUMMARY

Seasoned SAP Technical Consultant with over 8+ years of experience in working and spearheading multiple implementations, Support, and S/4 Conversion projects.

I aspire to learn and work on newer technologies in SAP, serve the organization with utmost dedication, and grow profitably in my career.

#### SKILLS

- Core ABAP Reports, Enhancements, Workflows, Web services, Odata, Adobe forms, Std Fiori Activation.
- ABAP on HANA AMDP, CDS views, Enhancements in S4
- PI/PO, CPI
- SPAU, SPDD, SPAU\_ENH, Custom code remediation

#### HIGHLIGHTS

- Extensive experience in SAP ABAP Core, including ALV reports, Adobe Forms, ECC enhancements, classical workflows, web services, OData services, and standard Fiori tile configurations.
- Proficient in utilizing ABAP 7.4 and newer syntax, including AMDP methods and CDS views.

# SRI SATHYA SAI ANIRUDH K

SAP Technical Consultant

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Jaya Engineering College

2012 - 2016

Bachelors of Degree in Computer science engineering with a CGPA of 7.9

#### Dr. Alagappa Matriculation higher secondary school

2012

Completed +2 grade (H.S.C) with 90%

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd – Associate Practice Lead, SAP Technical Practice

#### Public sector firms & Ministries, Saudi Arabia

Aug 2024 - Till date

- Promoted as an Associate practice lead for SAP Technical practice (ABAP) for PSF & Ministries vertical in Saudi Arabia region
- R&R revolves around in involving into pre-sales opportunities, responsible for technical delivery in projects, planning for resources in pipeline along with RMG team.
- Around 40 people report to me in technical vertical.

### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Technical Lead / ABAP Sr. Consultant S/4 HANA Conversion.

#### Customer – Ministry of Investments, Saudi Arabia

Dec 2023 - Jul 2024

- S/4 HANA Conversion from ECC to S/4 2022.
- · Lead entire technical team in this project.
- Scope involves migration to \$4 and converting their existing 15
  Web Dynpro applications to UI5 applications.
- Worked on Conversion activities and Odata services for building UI5 apps.
- Successfully implemented and completed Hypercare issues post live.

Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Technical Lead / ABAP Sr. Consultant

- Worked on multiple implementation projects & couple of \$/4 Conversion projects.
- Experienced with PI/PO and CPI on a key project, with a solid grasp of these middleware technologies and a keen interest in further developing expertise.
- Led a team of 3-5 members in a successful conversion project.
- Eager to expand my expertise in integrations, RAP, Work Zone, and other BTP-related technologies.
- Certified on Integration Suite & ABAP on HANA

#### CONTACT

PHONE: +91 7358731812

EMAIL:

Sai.anirudh95@gmail.com

#### HOBBIES

Learning Tabla & Harmonium Singing Bhajans Bike Drives Movies Taking part in Service activities of Sri Sathya Sai Seva Organization as an active Volunteer.

#### Customer – Ministry of Finance, Saudi Arabia (Onsite)

Feb 2022 - Nov 2023

- Ministry of Finance UGRP (Unified Government Resource Program) is a program under MOF's Vision 2030 to digitize the entire ministry and related entities under one ERP-UGRP. The Implementation team will be implementing and doing roll outs and we as part of the Operations team are responsible for Production Support.
- · Underwent 3 months of Transition phase.
- Most of the incidents are from Workflow issues and bugs in existing ABAP code.
- Worked on Odata services to integrate SF custom portlet data into S4 system and created reports to view the same. This is part of Eltizam reports which are used by customers to upload the documents downloaded from SAP to Eltizam portlet.
- Have worked on one of the custom Iflow for the above requirement and has a basic understanding of the CPI and has interest to explore and work more on Integrations via CPI and PIPO.
- Worked on creating a custom solution for Asset transfer with workflow as there is no standard workflow option.

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP ABAP Consultant Customer - Saudi Aramco.

Dec 2021- Jan 2022

- Aramco has implemented a custom solution named Supplier Performance Evaluation to evaluate suppliers / Contractors based on their performance.
- The project is about re-engineering existing solutions by fixing existing bugs, fine-tuning the code and work on new requirements.
- As part of this project, I lead myself and one more senior consultant and worked closely to analyze and identify bugs, modularize repetitive codes, and implemented the changes requested.
- The challenge was that there were no technical documents created by the implementation team and we were able to quickly step in and understand the solution based on the solution document and fixed the existing list of bugs and corrected those as per the Business requirements.
- Worked on Aramco's customer approval engine to fix workflow-related issues while triggering evaluations.

## Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Technical Lead / ABAP / PI Consultant Customer - Saudi Aramco Total Refining and Petrochemical Co.

Mar 2021 - Nov 2021

- Leading a team of 3 and working as PI/ABAP consultant in an Integration project.
- The Project involves integration between ARAMCO with its Joint venture SATORP wherein ARAMCO procures on behalf of SATORP. So, the integration involves sending back and forth the procurement data like PR's, PO's, GR etc. using the Web services created by SATORP.
- Developed both synchronous and asynchronous interfaces with SOAP to ABAP proxy scenario which includes graphical mapping.
- All the web services developed are exposed to the third party over the internet using HTTPS protocol and with server certificate exchange.

- Had worked on a unique scenario to upload & download the attachments to & from Open text content server.
- For Uploading attachments to open text from SAP we have used standard classes and methods which internally calls the SOAP services which is established already at the time of Open text implementation.
- For retrieving the attachments, we have used REST API of Open text and have consumed it in S4 system directly.

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP ABAP/ PI Consultant Customer - Emerson Electric

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021

- Worked as PI/ABAP Consultant in shipping optimization integration project with a team size of 2. The Backend SAP system is an IS-OIL implemented ECC system.
- The Project involves integration with SAP Aramco and Emerson's Synthesis system, a prediction model which optimizes and predicts the shipping nominations and its related operations.
- Developed 12 synchronous interfaces using SOAP to ABAP Proxy scenario. Out of 12, 10 interfaces are Outbound to SAP and 2 are Inbound to SAP.
- Developed staging tables to capture the inbound data and further developed interactive ALV reports to process the staged data.
- Followed customer coding standards while developing ABAP objects with SCI checks and extended program checks.

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Technical Lead / Consultant Customer – Ras Girtas Power Company, Qatar

Mar 2020 - Sep 2020

- Technical lead and a consultant for a team of three.
- The project is an S4 HANA conversion 1909 with Lift and shift strategy.
- Converted Sandbox, Development, Quality, and production systems by carrying out ATC Checks, SPAU, SPDD, Custom code remediation post conversion.
- Identified affected objects and created new developments to ensure the functionality in S4 as in ECC. E.g.: Enhancements done in Vendor master tables has been converted to BP.
- The existing system had MM, PM, HCM, FI modules implemented in ECC.

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Technical Lead / Consultant Customer – Ministry of Interior, Dammam (Onsite)

Aug 2019 - Feb 2020

- Had worked on a Rollout project for an already implemented \$4 system, for one of the Ministry of Interiors in Saudi Arabia at Customer locations in Dammam.
- The project had 3 members with me leading the Project on technical front.
- Analyzed the reports and dashboards which needs to be extended for the new company code and implemented.
- Since the customer is a Saudi government entity, the adobe forms developed were full of Arabic.

Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Associate Technical Consultant Customer – Ministry of Interior, Mekkah (Partial Onsite)

May 2018 – Jul 2019

- Worked as an ABAP consultant in implementing \$4 HANA 1709 greenfield for one of ministries of interiors, Saudi Arabia.
- Had the opportunity to work along with the team at onsite in partner location in Saudi Arabia.
- The S4 HANA public sector implementation had different modules like FI, MM, SRM, HCM, PM.
- Had developed custom interactive ALV reports, Dashboards for fund reservation in MM module, Standard workflow activation for FI funds management (Budget creation - FMX1), Material management, Custom enhancement in MIGO for MM-PM integration, custom developments in HR for Off cycle Payroll, Arabic adobe forms, providing custom developments in Fiori as GUI tiles, standard Fiori tile activations etc.
- Had worked on a complex Arabic adobe form called Form-29 which is a critical form for the customer.

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Associate Technical Consultant Customer – Saudi Industrial Development Fund (Onsite)

Dec 2017 - Feb 2018

- Worked as an ABAP consultant at customer's place along with the team.
- The Project involves additional module implementations like Erecruitment, PMS, Learning Solution, Cash management, BCM etc.
- Was solely responsible to work on a complex custom report which is very much critical for the customer which displays the company's overall Expenditure on Loans disbursements, investments in Treasury bonds, Revenues from Loans, etc., based on which financial planning for every year takes place.
- Developed SRM Adobe forms in Arabic and English, worked on few small enhancements in SRM and UAT fixes on the E-rec module and PMS module (custom development).

#### Kaar Technologies pvt.ltd - SAP Associate Technical Consultant Customer – Saudi Industrial Development Fund

Jun 2016 - Nov 2016

- Worked for a greenfield implementation of ECC on HANA in Saudi Arabia for a customer called Saudi Industrial Development Fund.
- The implementation involved modules like HR, MM, FI.
- Had developed Adobe forms, critical Custom reports for HR module like Bank file summary, Deductions and Bank Letter report.
- Fixed issues in Existing OData services developed.
- Developed a dashboard program using Module pool programming.

# Kotamraju, Sri Sathya Sai Anirudh +917358731812 sai.anirudh95@gmail.com